Mr Gao,
what happened?
I spilled some wine.
I'll go change my suit.
What happened to Mr Gao?
Oh no!
Mr Zhou,
Young Master Lu is back.
When did he come back?
I don't know.
Ah...
Mr. Li...
Mr. Li, you...
It's okay.
I fell by myself.
Lu Xu,
today is the press conference. What do you want to do?
Why did you hit Mr. Gao and Mr. Li?
Brother-in-law,
Mr. Gao and Mr. Li are profiteers.
As the person in charge, you don't care about it.
I, as the heir, can't just ignore it.
I just found out about it.
I'll handle it properly.
Lu Xu,
what are you doing here?
Haven't seen you in over half a year.
Did you miss me?
My dear sister,
of course, I'm here to give you and my brother-in-law
a big surprise.
Li Xiaorou,
it's about time.
Let's start the show.
Distinguished guests,
dear media friends,
good evening.
Thank you for taking the time
to join us here today.
Now, I'd like to announce
the Golden Thread Urban Visitor Series Fashion Show
officially begins!
Today, there are no unattainable runways,
only the must-have items you want to wear out.
We believe
real fashion is in your everyday wardrobe.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Maybe
I've been sitting too long.
My back hurts a bit.
Don't worry,
no one can shake your position.
Mr. Zhou,
we meet again.
Honey,
Jenny's designs are just so-so.
I really don't know what my mom was thinking,
giving her the position of chief designer.
Do you still
have that note?
Why haven't you contacted me?
Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight's fashion show comes to an end.
Thank you to everyone behind the scenes,
and to all of you here
for joining us on this
exciting journey of self-expression.
After the show,
now,
let's welcome
the next segment with applause.
Please welcome the head of Golden Thread,
Mr. Zhou Jian, to the stage.
What's going on?
Why is Lu Xu up there?
Dear guests and media friends,
welcome to the new product launch
of Golden Thread.
Today,
we'll not only showcase new products,
but also announce
two important things.
Once upon a time,
under the leadership of my mother, Annie,
Golden Thread became the leader in the industry.
From this year,
the Dark Fairy Tale series
will be our first step into the luxury market.
This lady, Jiang Li,
will become the chief designer
of Dark Fairy Tale.
Dark Fairy Tale's designer?
She's so young!
And,
she's also my fiancée.
What's going on?
He already has a fiancee?
What? A fiancee?
So sudden.
You're done.
She didn't leave with Lu Xu.
[Jiang Li,]
[let's meet up.]
So you're hiding here.
Name your price.
What?
Me and Lu Xu?
Don't play dumb with me.
You're just an unmarried wife.
Even if you wear the Lu family's wedding ring,
you're just a dog with a collar.
When the master doesn't throw you a bone,
you should learn to lie down
quietly.
The chief designer of Dark Fairy Tale
is not someone like you should aspire to.
Why are you laughing?
You people born in the clouds,
do you think you are more precious than others?
People like me, born in the mud,
without background or financial resources,
even if I grind the bones into dust,
I can't reach the gold powder under your feet.
Have you ever thought that
it's not because I'm Lu Xu's fiancée
that I can be the designer of Dark Fairy Tale,
but because I can be the designer of Dark Fairy Tale
to be his fiancée.
Not all efforts
in this world
can be rewarded.
Cinderella
only exists
in fairy tales.
Cinderella.
People who wear crystal high heels every day
are just dancing in shackles.
Lu Xu can be my fiancé, or not.
Who cares?
That will be 15.9 yuan.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It hurts.
Lu Qianqian, why do you hit me so hard?
Thank you.
This one is good.
Try it.
Thank you.
Your name is Jiang Li?
Young Master Shen, your pick-up line is so old-fashioned.
It doesn't match your age.
You remember me?
Everyone in the city knows you,
the heir of Shen Family.
Lu Xu left you here alone?
You were there just now?
Yes.
It's just a marriage of convenience.
He's not my guardian.
I'll do it.
The heir of the richest person in Lucheng
is eating rice ball in the convenience store at night.
This is more surprising than me
after being dumped at a convenience store meal.
The most ordinary things
are often the most delicious.
All right.
It's getting late.
I'm leaving.
Where do you live?
I'll give you a ride.
We'd better keep a distance.
After all,
I'm Lu Xu's fiancée.
Didn't I ask you to stay in Japan?
That place is too pretentious.
Living there is both fake and suffocating.
What's the point of staying there?
I'll ask Yanyan to tidy up a room for you.
Move back to the ancestral house.
I'm fine living in a hotel.
It's not good to live in the ancestral house.
I just heard from Wu that
you made a mess at the fashion show again.
Anyway, Jiang Li becoming the chief designer of Dark Fairy Tale
will be announced sooner or later.
I'm talking about your engagement to her.
I'm your only son.
Give the company to an outsider?
Lu Xu,
don't make any more messes for me to clean up.
Behave yourself
until I return from abroad.
Sister,
do you really miss me?
Mr. Lu,
didn't Jiang Li go missing?
I didn't know
she opened a live broadcast room with a virtual address.
Where's Zhou Jian?
I don't know.
I don't care if Jiang Li is alive or dead.
Find her.
Stop her.
Look!
Lu Qianqian is out!
Mr. Lu.
Wasn't Jiang Li missing?
Why did she suddenly reappear?
Mr. Lu.
Did you just find out
your husband cheated on you?
The press conference of Dark Fairy Tale is about to start.
Does Annie know about it?
Will it affect the company's listing?
When will Annie come back?
Mr. Lu,
there's a saying I like.
If heaven is not my home,
then hell
is my paradise.
Welcome to my paradise
and listen to my story.
Now,
it's just getting started.